- 瑞秋  履历表快用完了 - 你真想到 《大众机械》杂志社上班吗 - 如果你想要从事机械行业 那你就算找对地方了 那你就算找对地方了
- Rachel. We're running low on resumes. - You want a job with Popular Mechanics?  - Well, if you're gonna work for mechanics,
各位  我什么都得试试  我不能再当服务生了 我是说真的  我已厌倦微薄小费我已厌倦顾客不把我当人使唤
- Guys, I'm going for anything here. I can't be a waitress anymore. I mean it. I'm sick of the lousy tips. I'm sick of being called "Excuse Me."
- 瑞秋  这些你校对过吗  - 对  有问题吗 - 没事  他们对你高超的 "垫脑"技术定会印象深刻的   - 糟了  每一份上面都这样吗 没事  - 我肯定富士施乐打印机改掉一些了
- Rach, did you proofread these?- Yeah. Why? - Nothing. I'm sure they'll be impressed with your excellent "compuper" skills. - Oh, my God! Do you think it's on all of them? - No, I'm sure the Xerox machine caught a few.
-嗨  小伙子们  -嗨  - 嗨  姑娘们 需要什么吗
- Hey, guys. - Hey. - Hi, ladies. Can I get you anything?
- 信件带来了没  - 很多回复  - 真的吗 - 我们这儿当然还有烤饼  - 快念给我听
- Did you bring the mail? - Lots of responses. - Really? - Sure, we have scones left! Read them to me.
- "亲爱的格林小姐 "感谢您的申请  然而..."
- Dear Miss Greene: Thank you for your inquiry. "However"
-我们有苹果肉桂  -"亲爱的格林小姐" 好  好  不行
- We have apple cinnamon -"Dear Ms. Greene...." Yeah, yeah! No.
-怎么了  -你的信用卡账单不少呀 - 给我
- What? - Your Visa bill is huge! - Give me that.
我真不敢相信  琳达那么好  你为何不再和她约会  -我也不知道  -还是因为她说了 《摩登原始人》里的情节真有可能发生
- I can't believe you. Linda's so great. Why won't you go out with her? - I don't know. - ls this still about her..."The Flintstones could have really happened" thing?
不仅仅是那样  我要一个能让我有感觉  能让我心跳加速 ...能给我...  做小毛绒玩具吗 ?
It's not just that. I want someone who does something for me...who gets my heart pounding. Who makes me...Little playthings with yarn ？
- 什么 - 你是有多喜欢她 - 谁 - 阿蒂《发生何事》中那个犀利的妹妹   - 我早就不喜欢她了
- What? - Could you want her more?  - Who? - Dee, the sarcastic sister from What's Happening! - Look, I'm totally over her.
-嗨  -要咖啡吗 -不用加  -好的
- Hi! - Coffee? - No, we're fine. - Okay.
-闭嘴  -我们什么都没说  -怎么了  -昨晚乔伊哭了   -谢谢  -我们正在玩扑克牌  三点上有巧克力  看起来像是八点
- Shut up! - We're not saying anything.- What? - Joey cried last night.- Thank you. - We were playing poker, There was chocolate on the three. It looked like an eight.
可惜你没看到 他说"准备痛哭流涕吧"  结果哭的是他
You should have seen him. "Read them and weep!"And then he did.
- 你们怎么没和我们玩过扑克牌  - 对啊  为什么 这是性别歧视的问题吗 这是扑克  只有男人才能玩
- Now, how come you guys have never played poker with us? - Yeah, what is that?  Like some kind of sexist guy thing?  It's poker, so only guys can play?
不啊  女生也欢迎加人
No. Women can play.
那么为什么...这到底是为什么 快说  到底为什么
Then, what is it? Some kind of, like, some kind of, you know All right, what is it?
- 只是刚好女生没加入罢了 - 对  我们刚好找不到会玩扑克的女生 - 这个借口真烂  男生都是这种反应
There are just no women in our game. We just don't know any women who know how to play poker.  - That is such a lame excuse. It's a typical guy response.
请问你们谁会玩扑克牌 不会 -但你们可以教我们  -不要
- Do you know how to play? - No. - But you could teach us. - No.
现在开始抽牌。
Okay, so now we draw cards.
我不需要对吧  因为我一把顺  -你太棒了  -恭喜了
- So I wouldn't need any. I have a straight. - Oh, good for you! - Congratulations!
-菲比  你要几张  -我需要两张  黑桃十和梅花六 - 菲比  不  你不能这么要 - 等等  我有你要的黑桃十  给 - 谢谢!
- Pheebs, how many do you want? - I just need two. The 10 of spades and the 6 of clubs. - Pheebs. No, you can't - Wait! I have the 10 of spades! Here. - Thanks!
- 不  你不能那样 - 没关系  我不需要  我要四张同点  - 哦 是吗
- No, you can't do that. - It's ok. Don't need them. I'm going for fours. - Oh, you're.
开始吧 Here we go. 我们有炸鲑鱼圈配蔬菜沙拉 We've got salmon roulettes and assorted crudites.
- 莫妮卡  你在干什么 这是打扑克  食物名称不能超过两个字 得是薯片  沙司  百奇之类的
Monica. What are you doing? This is a poker game. You can't serve food with more than one syllable.  It's got to be like chips or dip or pretz.
- 现在发牌的人... 我们会了  开始玩真的吧 高赌资  大笔钱 你当真  菲比刚丢出一双十一点 就因为他们好像不开心
- OK, so at this point, the dealer... - We got it. Let's play for real. High stakes. Big bucks! - You sure? Phoebe just threw away two jacks because they didn't look happy.
但我准备好了  发牌吧
But I'm ready. So just deal.
各位  最后通知  乔伊 三点 八点 八点  三点  好的  不错
Okay, last-minute lesson! Joey.... Three. Eight. Eight. Three. All right, very good.
- 该死  该死  该死  - 我明白了  你们在骗人  - 骗什么 -骗你们牌有多好  -那是唬人 什么是唬 不就是骗的同义字吗
- Damn it, damn it, damn it!- I see, so you were lying. - About what? - About how good your cards were. - I was bluffing. -  And what is bluffing? Is it not another word for lying?
- 抱歉  我不能再玩了 我得在明天工作前打好履历表 - 瑞秋  我们得算帐  -什么定居   - 在维吉尼亚的詹姆斯敦殖民地 乔治三世把它给了我们美国所以...   -是扑克  瑞秋  你欠我们钱  -对哦
- Sorry to break up this party, but I've got to go fax resumes before work. - Settle what? - The Jamestown colony of Virginia. See, King George is giving us the land....- The game, Rachel. You owe us money. - Right.
这样吧  兄弟们  这是她们第一次打扑克  别和她们计较钱了 - 那怎么行  我们会付钱的 - 莫妮卡  我本来准备好另一个回复了
You know what, you guys? It's their first time, why don't we just forget about the money, alright? - Hell, no. We'll pay!  - Monica, I had another answer all ready.
- 你们知道吗  我们要重来一盘 - 我无所谓  钱多不嫌烧手
- And you know what? We want a rematch. - Well that's fine with me. Could use the money.
这么说你们的组合家具基本上 都是用朋友的钱买来的
So basically, you get your ya-yas by taking money from your friends.
没错  而且我是在"宜家"家具商场买的 得自己动手装  但便宜一点
Yes, and I get my ya-yas from IKEA. You have to put them together yourself, but they cost a little less.
瑞秋  这是扑克牌  玩就是要赢  如果我想赢  就得有人输
Look, Rach, this is poker. I play to win. For me to win, others have to lose.
- 如果想和我玩牌  就别指望我做个好人 因为牌一发出 - 然后呢 - 我就不是个好人
If you're gonna play pocker with me, don't expect me to be a nice guy. Because once those cards are dealt.... - Yeah? - I'm not a nice guy.
- 各位  吃吧  - 这是从"我爱瑞秋披萨屋"买的吗
- All right, boys, let's eat. - Did you get that from the "I Love Rachel Pizzeria"?
- 还没笑够啊 - 得了吧  不然你为何学黑道电影讲话 "玩起牌来  我就不是个好人" - 你扯太远了
You still on that? - Come on. What was with that Black Bart speech? "When I play poker, I'm not a nice guy."  - You're way off.
- 我可不这么认为  因为我觉得你爱她 - 不  或许我曾对她有爱意 但我已心灰意冷  我只是
- No, I don't think so, because I think you love her! - No. I might have had feelings for her at one time.  Not anymore.  I just
马塞尔  你拿那张光盘要干嘛 不能再放上去  马塞尔 如果你按那个按钮  你可有大麻烦了
Marcel! Where are you going with that disk? You are not putting that on again. Marcel!  If you press that button,you are in very big trouble.
- 你能相信罗斯刚刚那么混蛋吗 - 我懂  - 他的好胜心最强了 - 什么 -  - 拜托
- You believe what a jerk Ross was being? - Yeah, I know. - He can get really competitive. - What?  - "Hello, kettle, This is Monica. You're black!" - Please!
- 我没像罗斯那么过分 - 我反对  "画图猜字"那次呢 - 我不是故意的 我在做手势时盘子不慎从手里滑落了
- I'm not as bad as Ross. - I beg to differ. The Pictionary incident? - That wasn't an incident.  I was gesturing and the plate slipped out of my hand.
-我有面试机会了  -不是吧  在哪  萨克斯第五大道精品店[顶级百货公司] 哦  瑞秋  这就像是母舰在呼唤你归队
- I got an interview! - You're kidding! Where? - Saks Fifth Avenue. - Oh, Rachel! - It's like the mother ship is calling you home.
-是什么工作  -采购助理 我要靠购物...来谋生了
- What's the job? - Assistant buyer.  I would be shopping! For a living!
艾莉丝姑姑来了  她从五岁便开始玩牌  她说的每个字我们都得牢记在心
That's Aunt Iris. This woman's been playing poker since she was 5.You've got to listen to every word she says.
- 托尼·兰德尔[著名演员]死了吗 - 什么  没有吧  - 现在说不定  -因为我好像开车撞到他了  -真的吗 不  唬你们的  这是第一课
- ls Tony Randall dead? - What? I don't think so. - He may be now. - Because I think I hit him with my car. - My God, really? - No, that's bluffing. Lesson number one.
- 我告诉你们 打扑克时听到的每个字都是狗屁 耳环挺好看  - 谢...
- Let me tell you something. Everything you hear at a poker game is pure crap! Nice earrings. - Thank you.
- 坐吧  姑娘们 - 艾莉丝姑姑  这是菲比  这是瑞秋 - 听着  我停车要收费的  快点开始吧
- Girls, sit down. - Aunt lris, this is Phoebe and Rachel. - Listen, I'm parked at a meter. Let's do it. Okay?
- 罗斯  求你了  我们能听点别的吗 - 好吧 我今晚可要为此付出代价了
- Ross, could we please listen to anything else?  - All right. I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
- 伙计们  猜猜看怎么了 - 第五位牙医妥协了他们现在都推销"三叉戟"牌口香糖了吗 该品牌广告中称五个牙医有四个推荐它
- Hi. Guys, guess what?  - The fifth dentist caved, and now they're all recommending Trident?
不  是面试，她喜欢我  她绝对非常喜欢我 我们谈了能有两个半小时 我们对服饰的品味一致我还和她的表妹一起去过夏令营  这工作太完美了  我可以胜任 太好了  太棒了
No, the interview! She loved me! She absolutely loved me. We talked like two and a half hours.  We've the same taste in clothes. And I went to camp with her cousin. The job is perfect! I can do this.  That's great! That's wonderful.
- 然后她给我讲了个超好笑的故事 - 很好  行了  假设你讲完了我们笑完了 玩牌吧
- Then she told the funniest story...  - Great, you will tell us and we'll laugh. Let's play poker!
- 各位听好  我们谈过此事 如果你们不想玩 我们完全了解 对 我们可以玩别的游戏 比如说看图猜字- 真好笑
- Listen you guys, we talked about it and if you don't wanna play, we completely understand Yes, we can play some other game. Like Pictionary?  - Very funny.
- 但我们想再试一次打扑克  对吧姑娘们  - 没错  我想是的
- But I think we'd like to give poker another try. Shall we, ladies?- Yes, I think we should.
- 瑞秋  需要我来洗牌吗 - 不用了  没事  我想自己试试
- Rach. Do you want me to shuffle those? - No. That's okay, I'm gonna give it a go.
这样菲比欠7块5  莫妮卡欠10块 瑞秋  你欠15块
So Pheebs owes $7. 50. Monica owes $10.00. And Rachel, you owe 15 big ones!
谢谢教我们"美女斜眼暗示法" 兄弟们  我们平时玩牌的时候也该试试
Thanks for teaching us Cross-Eyed Mary. You guys, we gotta play that at our regular game.
- 给  这是我的7块5不过我告诉你们  这钱已受到诅咒 - 什么  - 我对它下了咒 花这些钱的人会倒大楣 - 无所谓  我接受 我反正够倒楣的了 这样的话  我还可以看场电影分散分散
All right, here's my $7.50. But I think you should know that this money is cursed. - What? - I cursed it!  Now bad things will happen to the spender. - That's alright, I'll take it. Bad things happen to me anyway.  This way, I can split them up with a movie.
- 现在只差格林牌扑克机欠了15块没给了 - 男生都这副德行 "我是男人  我有小鸡鸡" 我得靠赢钱才能征服女人"
So that just leaves the big Greene poker machine, who owes 15. It's so typical. "I'm a man! I have a penis! ""I have to win money to exert my power over women!"
- 知道吗  这事没完  我们还要跟你们再战 我们大获全胜  你们一败涂地你们跪地求饶  我们仰天大笑我们会赢走你们的每一分钱 你们会永远恨死自己 - 你这有点给我拆台啊  莫妮卡
- You know. This isn't over. We'll play you again.  We'll win. You'll lose.  You'll beg. We'll laugh. We'll take every last dime you have. And you'll hate yourselves forever!  - Kind of stepped on my point there, Mon.
- 姑娘们  你们想现在就把钱给我们吗 这样我们就不必浪费时间 装模作样地玩一场了 - 不  就这样 我倒要看看谁笑到最后  猴子男
- So, you gals wanna give us your money now? That way, we don't have to go through the formality of actually playing. -  No, that's fine. We'll see who has the last laugh, monkey boy.
聊完了没  可以开始玩真的了吗 你们看  独眼杰克一直看着我
- Done with chitchat? Ready for serious poker? - You guys, look! The one-eyed jack follows me wherever I go.
好  玩真的 Right. Serious poker.
-等下  你要上哪儿去  -卫生间 你想上厕所还是玩牌  我想上厕所
- Excuse me. Where are you going? - To the bathroom. - Want to go to the bathroom or play poker? - Go to the bathroom.
-好吧  我去订披萨  -不行 我还在等面试回信 他们的店9点关门  那时候再吃吧 - 行  那我就含块薄荷糖提神
- Well, I'm gonna order a pizza. - No! I'm waiting to hear from that job. The store closes at 9:00. Eat then. - That's fine. I'll just have a Tic Tac to hold me over.
- 来吧  辛辛那提玩法  下注吧 - 太好了或者不太好
- All right. Cincinnati. No blinds. Everybody,ante. - ... Yes!  Or no.
你的钱是我的了  格林 你的裤门没拉  盖勒
- All right! Your money's mine, Greene. - Your fly's open, Geller.
- 你们知道我刚发现什么吗 "杰克"就是把"扑克"中的"扑"换掉  是巧合吗 - 这么说"巧合"就是"茄盒"变过来的啊
- You guys know what I just realized? Joker is poker with a "J"! Coincidence? - That's jo-incidence with a "C"!
-菲比  -我不跟了  -我跟  -我也跟 我也跟  你拿什么牌 你最好赶紧洗完澡  因为我要冲马桶了
- Phoebe? - Yeah, I'm out.- I'm in. - Me too. - Me too. What do you got? You better hop out of the shower, because I got a flush.
行了  行了  行了 滚回来吧小子  因为我拿了四张六 我有四张六  我赢了 我真的赢了  天哪
Well, well, well! Hop back in, bucko, because I got four sixes! I got four sixes! I won! I actually won! Oh, my God!
你们知道吗  我要把小罗斯堆起来 我想这是罗斯的  那个也是罗斯的 你的钱都归了我  再也别想见到它
You know what? I'll make a little Ross pile. I think that one was Ross'. And I think that one was Ross'. Well, I have got your money And you'll never see it
你的裤门还没拉  我骗到你低头看
And your fly's still open. I made you look
-我跟  -我肯定跟 莫妮卡  跟还是不跟 我讨厌玩牌
- I'm in. - I couldn't be in-er.  Monica, in or out? I hate this game!
- 乔伊  你呢 - 我输得像是个廉价妓女还被一个  满脸伤痕的胖子对着肚子踹了一脚 ...  我不跟
- Joey, your bet. - I fold like a cheap hooker who got hit in the stomach...by a fat guy with sores on his face. I'm out.
- 罗斯  - 我确定跟 - Ross? - I'm very in.
- 钱德勒  - 绝对不跟 - 我也一样 瑞秋?
- Chandler? - Couldn't be more out.  - Me too. Rachel?
我不但跟而且还要加注 I will see you and I'll raise you.
- 如何 还想再浪费钱吗  - 这回肯定不会  来吧  给我看牌 - 我不会说的  - 给我看 -不  - 给我看  - 把你的手拿开  - 我约会时常常这样
- What do you say, wanna waste another buck? - No, not this time. So, what did you have - I'm not telling. - Show them. - No. - Show them! - Get your hands out of there! - I've had dates like this.
- 天啊  你真是输不起的家伙 你的脸涨得好红 太阳穴青筋毕露 - 而且这件上衣跟裤子一点不搭
Boy, you really can't stand to lose, can you? Your whole face is getting red. Veins popping out of your temple! - Plus, that shirt doesn't really match those pants.
- 首先  我不会输的  - 你输定了
- First of all. I'm not losing. - You're definitely losing.
你好  瑞秋·格林 不好意思  这是有关工作的电话 芭芭拉  你好吗
Hello. Rachel Greene. Excuse me. It's about the job! Barbara, hi! How are you?
不  我理解  不  我没事  快别这么说 但如果还有其他职位缺人  请... 喂
No, I understand. Come on. No, I'm fine. Don't be silly. Yeah. But if anything else opens up, please…… Hello?
我很遗憾,瑞秋 工作机会肯定有的是
Sorry, Rach.  There's gonna be lots of other stuff.
好的 玩到哪儿了？五张牌抽法 11点算大 大家下注
Okay.  Where were we?  Five-card draw.  Jacks are better. Nothing wild. Everybody, ante.
-瑞秋  别再玩了  -要玩  下注
- Look, Rach, we don't have to do this. - Yes, we do.
-好吧  不跟  -不跟
- All right. Check. - Check.
-我跟5毛钱  -跟 我跟
- I'm in for 50 cents. - Call.  I'm in.
- 我跟你5毛 而且我要加5块钱 ... - 我以为5毛是上限 - 我刚失去工作机会  所以想加5块  各位有问题吗 - 当然没有  - 没有  - 我们收牌 - 输家？
- I see your 50 cents... and I raise you $5. - I thought it was a 50-cent limit. - I just lost a job, I'd like to raise it $5.Does anyone have a problem with that?  - Not at all. - No. We're out.  - Loser?
-我收牌了  -你收牌是什么意思 你不是说"一旦发牌  我就不是好人"吗  还是只是信口胡说？
- No, I fold. - What do you mean, you fold? I thought that, "Once the cards are dealt, I'm not a nice guy."Were you just full of it?
- 我跟  - 要几张牌  - 一张
- I'm in. - How many do you want? - One.
庄家两张  - 下多少  - 我下2块 - 我跟你2块  再加你 ... 20块 ...
Dealer takes two.- What do you bet? - I bet $2. - Okay. I see your $2...and I raise you...20.
我跟你20块 再加到25块 ...
I see your $20... raise you $25.
- 跟你25块  莫妮卡  拿我的皮包来 - 瑞秋  里面没钱  那就拿你的皮包来 - 给你  祝你好运  - 谢谢
- I see your $25 and Monica, get my purse. - Rachel, there's nothing in it. - Okay, then get me your purse. - Here you go. Good luck! - Thank you.
- 跟你25块  再加  ...7块  - 是17块!
- I saw your $25 and I raise you......seven. - teen!
乔伊  我有点囊中羞涩 没关系  罗斯  有什么问题可以问我 （有什么可害羞的？）
- Joey, I'm a little shy. - That's okay, Ross. You can ask me.
- 要多少  - 15块  - 这里有10块  - 我这里有5块 - 谢谢  - 祝你好运
- What do you need? - 15. - Here's 10. - I got 5. - Thank you. - Good luck.
- 再加十七块 你拿什么牌 - 三张同点加一对  - 败给你了
- I am calling your 17. What do you got? - Full house. - You got me.
-那确实很难赢  -我以为我们会赢 没有好牌就是没有好牌 瞧 她多开心
- That's tough to beat. - I thought we had it! When you don't have the cards, you don't have the cards. But look how happy she is.
-航空邮件  -飞机  机场  《75空难》  《77空难》  《79空难》 时间到 Time's up! "再见了...小鸟"[电影名]那是小鸟 那就是小鸟!
- Airmail. - Airplane. Airport. Airport '75!Airport '77! Airport '79!  - Bye Bye Birdie!  - That's a bird? That's a bird!
- 该我了 开始 - 豆子  豆子《生命中不能承受之轻》   - 答对了? 这样就能猜中
- Okay, it's my turn. Go!  - Bean! Bean! The Unbearable Lightness of Being! - That you get? - That you get?!